

# Ismail Bentabet

Software Engineer

- . +213 0794753644
- Algeria
- ismailbentabett@gmail.com
- https://github/ismailbentabett

# **Summary**

A Multi-Talented multidisciplinary
Freelance Full-Stack Software
developer and UI/UX Designer,
Computer Science Student,
Business enthusiast with
Entrepreneurial goals, and Co-Founder
Of

Shortcut, I have 3 years of experience in software development with multiple tech stacks using the latest design trends with the goal of ultimate success

# Skills

PHP LARAVEL	8
Description of this skill set	
Flutter	6
Description of this skill set	
Tailwind	9
Description of this skill set	
Devops	5
Description of this skill set	
Figma	9
Description of this skill set	
React	4
Description of this skill set	
Vue	9
Description of this skill set	
HTML & CSS	10
Description of this skill set	
JS & TS	9
Description of this skill set	
C# . NET	7
Description of this skill set	
Node	8
Description of this skill set	

Angular

Description of this skill set

# Work experience

# • Chief Technology Officer (CTO)

#### Shortcut

2022-03 - present

Your most impressive achievements here.

# Senior Full stack software developer

#### **Shortcut**

2020-08 - present

Your most impressive achievements here.

#### Co-Founder

#### Shortcut

2020-07 - present

Your most impressive achievements here.

# Software Engineer

#### Sig Service

2022-05 - 2022-10

Your most impressive achievements here.

#### Education

# Bachelor's degree

#### Dr Tahar MOULAY University of Saida

Start date - 2022-06

Dr Tahar MOULAY University of Saida Bachelor's degree, Computer Science • (January 2018 - June 2022)

# Qualifications

Front End Development

Back End Development

Mobile & Desktop Development

UI/UX Design

Entrepreneur & Social Media Manager

Digital Marketer & E-Commerce Consultant

# Languages

French	10	Arabic	9
Description of this skill set		Description of this skill set	
English	8		
Description of this skill set			

# Certifications

- The Fundamentals of digital Marketing By Google
- EF SET English Certificate [C2 Proficient]